<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="no_repository">You haven\'t set the ROM repository from the settings menu. Clicking on Ok the Settings window will appear.</string>
	<string name="changelog_toast">Long press to view the changelog</string>
	<string name="repository_changed_toast">The ROM repository URL has been changed</string>
	<string name="repository_unreachable">The ROM repository is currently unreachable. Please check it, or try again later.</string>
	<string name="barcode_scanner_not_found">It seems that Barcode Scanner (com.google.zxing.client.android) is not installed.</string>
	<string name="wipe_cache_message">The phone will reboot into recovery mode and it will perform the wipe.</string>
	<string name="wipe_data_message">The phone will reboot into recovery mode and it will perform the wipe.</string>
	<string name="backup_rom_message">The phone will reboot into recovery mode and it will perform the backup.</string>
	<string name="recovery_message">The phone will reboot into recovery mode.</string>
	<string name="repository_file_not_found">The file you\'re trying to download is unreachable or unavailable. Please try again later, or contact the repository maintainer.</string>
	<string name="upgrade_confirmation">Do you want to apply the update right now?</string>
	<string name="modname_mismatch">Your mod seems to be different from the repository one. You\'ll be able to download only the full versions.</string>
	<string name="version_descriptor_not_found_message">The version descriptor file has not been found.</string>
	<string name="rom_is_updated">Your ROM is already updated to the latest version.</string>
	<string name="anon_send_message">Would you like to help the developer know more about the ROM name and version you\'ll download? You can anonymously send this data. If you want, you can find the setting under the preferences pane.</string>
	<string name="repo_phone_mismatch">Your phone is not compatible with this repository.</string>
	<string name="no_repository_available">There are actually no available repositories. Share yours sending anonymous data!</string>
	<string name="error_model_mismatch">Attention: you\'re attempting to install a ROM not designed for your phone model. Abort.</string>
	<string name="error_download_list">There was an error downloading the list of the repositories. Please try again later.</string>
	<string name="error_backup_folder_empty">You have no backups in the current backup folder.</string>
	<string name="error_backup_folder_doesnt_exist">The backup folder doesn\'t appear to exist. Check it in your settings.</string>
	<string name="error_download_file">There was an error downloading the file.</string>
	<string name="wipe_sdext_too">Do you want to wipe the SD-EXT partition too?</string>
	<string name="confirm_restore_backup">Are you sure you want to restore this backup?</string>
	<string name="ask_backup_wipe">It seems that your ROM name differs from the one you\'ve downloaded. Do you want to wipe, or backup and wipe the user data before updating?</string>
	<string name="info_no_downloads">There are no files in the download directory</string>
</resources>
